Er. NARESH SINGH DHAMI

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/naresh-singh-dhami-461bb8132

Gmail: <u>ndhami74@gmail.com</u> **Contact:** (+977-9864459829/9863449852)



SUMMARY

A licensed Civil Engineer with more than four years of working experience in the field of hydropower/Building design, construction supervision, and management. Committed to providing high-quality services for the projects and primarily focused on health, environment, and safety.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth: 2nd July 1995 Marital Status: Married

Nationality: Nepalese Permanent Address: 02-Malikarjun, Darchula

Temporary Address: Lokanthali, Bhaktapur Language: Nepali, Hindi, English, Japanese(N3)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Civil Engineer (株式森会社 本組: May 2022 – Present)

Since May 2022, I have been working as a Civil Engineer at Morimotogumi Company Limited (株式森本組) resides in Tokyo, Japan.

Responsibilities:

- Residential/Commercial building demolition supervision
- Construction safety, Planning and, Management
- Road and underground sewage construction supervision

Civil Engineer (Nepal Electricity Authority Engineering Company Ltd: Dec 2021 – April 2022)

Working as a Civil Engineer (Site Based) for the construction supervision of 25MW Grid Connected Solar Project, Nuwakot, holding the following responsibilities.

- Quality assurance and planning
- Construction supervision and monitoring
- Coordination with contractor and client for timely completion of the project

Civil Engineer (Rural water supply project:- CRT/N)

Detailed survey, design, and estimation of water supply project resides in Sindhuli district. The project was sponsored by the **Centre for Rural Technology**, **Nepal** (**CRT/N**) and was designed for around 120 households.

- The initial survey, final survey, and household survey
- Detailed design of the project
- Billing and cost estimation of the project.

Civil Engineer (G.R. Design and Builders Pvt. Ltd: Feb 2021 – Aug 2021)

The company was established by energetic engineers from Kathmandu University in the year 2017. Joined the company at the start of February 2020 and received a huge oportunity to show the skills and knowledge acquired during the previous two years as a Site Engineer. The company was primarily focused on the field of survey, design, analysis, and construction supervision.

Responsibilities as a Civil Engineer:

- Responsible for building planning, design and analysis
- Hydraulic design of micro-hydropower plant
- Construction supervision
- Billing, cost estimation, and preparation of schedule.

Site Engineer (Angel Engineering Consultancy Pvt. Ltd: Nov 2017 - Dec 2020)

Initially started as a Site Engineer, responsible for construction supervision of headworks and underground structure for almost one year, later appointed as a Site Engineer for Powerhouse construction. For the next one and half years, I was involved in technical as well as construction supervision of the powerhouse.

Responsibilities as a Site Engineer:

- Enforce the relevant safety rules at the site
- Conduct daily briefings with contractor team members to follow up and report on the work progress to anticipate any possible delays with regard to planned tasks
- Take immediate corrective action to avoid any cumulative effect of such deviation and recover the delay in finishing the task in due time
- Coordinate with the handing over of completed works to the client and completion of the necessary rectification works
- Evaluate and resolve any discrepancies and problems arising during construction which affect the quality of works performed
- Coordinate with the QA/QC department to prepare an inspection test plan (ITP)
- Maintain quality of activities of work and material by teaming up with the QC department
- Billing, verification and other various working schedules.

Civil Engineer (Sahan Engineering Concern Pvt. Ltd: Jun 2017 - Nov 2017)

Responsibilities:

- Selection of the feasible route for the transmission line
- Coordination with the local people for the proper placement of transformer and HT tower
- Manipulation of survey data and preparation of design drawings
- Billing, verification, and cost estimation.

Intern Engineer (Sanjen Hydropower Company Ltd: Apr 2017 - May 2017)

Started my professional Engineering career as an Intern Engineer at Sanjen Hydroelectric Project, 42.5MW. Involved in construction supervision of different hydropower components (surface as well as underground).

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

2017: Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering (First Division)

• Kathmandu University (KU), Dhulikhel, Kavre

2013: Intermediate Level in Science (First Division)

• NAST HSS, Dhangadhi, Kailali

2011: School Leaving Certificate (First Division)

Shree Malikarjun Higher Secondary School, Premnagar, Darchula

SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

- Maintain Quality of materials and activities
- Keeping good relationships and values
- Provide orientation to the employee on technical details of the construction
- Prepare work planning and resource management
- Civil 3D, SAP2000, STAAD Pro, SketchUp, SW_DTM, ETABS (CSI Details, CSI Safe), Microsoft Office package, Smart Road, Revit 2018 (BIM), Primavera and Good knowledge of Mini-Hydro Survey and Design Tools (Design Aids)
- Programming Language: C, C++.

CERTIFICATION

I the undersigned certify that to the best of knowledge and belief, these curriculum vitae correctly describe my qualification, my experience, and me. I understand that any wilful misstatement described herein may lead to disqualification or dismissal if employed.

REFERENCES

Name: Mandeep Dhonju Name: Diwash Rai

Designation: Project Co-ordinator Designation: Project Manager Email: mandeepdhoj@gmail.com Email: thediwash@gmail.com

Angel Engineering Consultancy Pvt. Ltd. Kalanga Gad Hydroelectric Project, 15.33MW